Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series X: Audio-Visual Material, 1957-2009
  - Subseries X:A: Audio Cassettes, 1968-2009
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn, You Can’t Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Education and Activism, Feb 13, 1995 (Box 74, Cassette 109)
    - David Barsamian: "Corporate Power, Profits Before People" (Santa Cruz, CA), Oct 13, 1995 (Box 74, Cassette 110)
    - Howard Zinn: A People’s History of the United States (Portland, OR), Nov 20, 1995 (Box 74, Cassette 111)
    - City Arts of San Francisco: Alice Walker and Howard Zinn in Discussion on Writing and Activism, Hosted by Maya Angelou (San Francisco, CA), [1995] (Box 74, Cassette 112)
    - Women’s Foundation of California / City Arts: Alice Walker in Discussion with Howard Zinn, Jan 17, 1996 (Box 74, Cassette 113)
    - WBAI: Howard Zinn - Lecture on History, Education and Objectivity (Fullerton College, Fullerton, CA) / Chris Whent Radio Show, Oct 12, 1996/Jun 6, 1992 (Box 74, Cassette 114)
    - Alice Walker: My Life as My Self, 1996 (Box 74, Cassette 115)
    - KPFA: Anything We Love Can Be Saved - Mothers’ Day Eve with Alice Walker (King Middle School, Berkeley, CA), May 10, 1997 (Box 74, Cassette 116)
    - WORT: A Public Affair - Howard Zinn Interviewed by James Carrott on You Can’t Be Neutral on a Moving Train, Jul 15, 1997 (Box 74, Cassette 117)
    - KPFA: Mario Savio Memorial Lecture - Howard Zinn "The Possibility of Hope: Our Legacy from the Sixties," University of California, Berkeley, CA, Nov 13, 1997 (Box 74, Cassette 118)
    - WORT: A Public Affair - Howard Zinn (Interview on the Uses of History), Nov 18, 1997 (Box 74, Cassette 119)
    - Howard Zinn: Lecture on the Uses of History (Wisconsin Historical Society, Madison, WI), Nov 18, 1997 (Box 74, Cassette 120)
    - Howard Zinn: Lecture on History, Politics and Objectivity (Portland, OR), Jan 22, 1998 (Box 74, Cassette 121)
    - Howard Zinn: One Hundred Years of U.S. Imperialism (Old Cambridge Baptist Church, Cambridge, MA), Jun 30, 1998 (Box 74, Cassette 122)
    - Alternative Radio: Eqbal Ahmad - "Terrorism: Theirs and Ours" (Boulder, CO), Oct 12, 1998 (Box 74, Cassette 123)
    - Alternative Radio: Eqbal Ahmad - Boulder Interviews (Boulder, CO), Oct 12, 1998-Oct 13, 1998 (Box 74, Cassette 124)
    - People’s Tribune Radio: Howard Zinn, A Working Class Citizen’s Economic Bill of Rights, Also Includes Nelson Peery, Oct 1998 (Box 74, Cassette 125)
    - Howard Zinn: Bringing Democracy Alive (University of Colorado, Denver, CO) Tape 1, 1998 (Box 74, Cassette 126)
    - Howard Zinn: Bringing Democracy Alive (University of Colorado, Denver, CO) Tape 2, 1998 (Box 74, Cassette 127)
    - WNYC: New York and Company - Howard Zinn (Interview), Jan 15, 1999 (Box 74, Cassette 128)
    - WUSB: Critique - Howard Zinn (Interview, Stony Brook, NY), [Feb 1, 1999] (Box 74, Cassette 129)
    - Alternative Radio: Howard Zinn - War and Democracy (Chestnut Hill, MA), Nov 11, 1999 (Box 74, Cassette 130)
    - Common Courage Press: "Zinn at the Heart of History: An Interview with Howard Zinn by Greg Bates on Objectivity and Optimism", 1999 (Box 74, Cassette 131)
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn (Interview, Stony Brook, NY), Jan 29, 2000 (Box 74, Cassette 132)
    - WNYC: New York and Company - Interviews on Howard Zinn on History and Howard Zinn on War, [2000] (Box 74, Cassette 133)
    - Alternative Radio: Arundhati Roy - "A Writer’s Place in Politics" (Amherst, MA), Feb 15, 2001 (Box 74, Cassette 134)
    - Alternative Radio: Howard Zinn - "Artists in a Time of War" (Massachusetts College of Art, Boston, MA), Oct 10, 2001 (Box 74, Cassette 135)
    - Alternative Radio: Howard Zinn - "Artists in a Time of War" (Massachusetts College of Art, Boston, MA), Oct 10, 2001 (Box 74, Cassette 135 dup)
    - WMBR: Anti-War Rally in Boston / Nov 2001 News (Democracy Rising Tour and Day of Mourning), Oct 12, 2001/Nov 2001 (Box 74, Cassette 136)
    - WAMU: Howard Zinn Interviewed by Diane Rehm on Terrorism and War, the Anti-War Movement and Alternatives to War (American University, Washington, DC), Jul 11, 2002 (Box 74, Cassette 137)
    - Howard Zinn: Interview on “A Break-in for Peace,” Article on the Camden 28 Published in The Progressive (July 2002), Jul 22, 2002 (Box 74, Cassette 138)
    - WBUR / NPR: The Connection - "Where’s the Opposition?: The Left’s Position on the Iraq War" (includes Peter Lems, Leo Ribuffo and Congresswoman Barbara Lee), Sep 17, 2002 (Box 74, Cassette 139)
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn - Interview (Stony Brook, NY), May 19, 2003 (Box 74, Cassette 140)
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn - Interview (Stony Brook, NY), Mar 28, 2005 (Box 74, Cassette 141)
    - WAMU: Howard Zinn Interviewed by Diane Rehm on Voices of a People’s History of the United States (American University, Washington, DC), May 2, 2005 (Box 74, Cassette 142)
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn - Interview on A Power Governments Cannot Suppress (Stony Brook, NY), Jan 20, 2007 (Box 74, Cassette 143)
    - KVSC Newswatch: Howard Zinn Interview on Voices of a People’s History of the United States, Dec 13, 2009 (Box 74, Cassette 144)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Race and Law, Oct 12 (Box 74, Cassette 145)
    - Dial a Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview (also includes music and other interviews), undated (Box 74, Cassette 146)
    - Diane Valcourt’s Audio Journal for Howard Zinn (PO 394), undated (Box 74, Cassette 147)
    - Documentary on Emma Goldman, undated (Box 74, Cassette 148)
    - Emma: A Play in Two Acts about Emma Goldman, American Anarchist by Howard Zinn: Performance in French, undated (Box 74, Cassette 149)
    - Eqbal Ahmed on Progressive Movements in Pakistan Tape 4, undated (Box 74, Cassette 150)
    - “Freedom and Democracy”: Spoken Word by Howard Zinn and Music by Steve Lutke and James Voris, undated (Box 74, Cassette 151)
    - “Freedom and Democracy”: Spoken Word by Howard Zinn and Music by Steve Lutke and James Voris, undated (Box 74, Cassette 151 dup)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Bacon’s Rebellion (poor audio quality), undated (Box 74, Cassette 152)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Central America and Just and Unjust Wars, undated (Box 74, Cassette 153)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Civil Disobedience Versus Voting (Tactics) / Bill Baird: Lecture to Howard Zinn’s Class / Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Daniel Berrigan, undated (Box 74, Cassette 154)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Political Theory and Ideology, undated (Box 74, Cassette 155)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on the State and the Individual / Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Human Nature, undated (Box 74, Cassette 156)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Tactics (Tape 1) / Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Women’s Suffrage, undated (Box 74, Cassette 157)
    - Howard Zinn: Interview with David Barsamian, undated (Box 74, Cassette 158)
    - Howard Zinn and Studs Terkel in Discussion: Introduced by Alice Walker (Berkeley, CA), undated (Box 74, Cassette 159)
    - Howard Zinn and Studs Terkel in Discussion: Introduced by Alice Walker (edited, Berkeley, CA), undated (Box 74, Cassette 160)
    - Howard Zinn: Unidentified [Microcassette], undated (Box 74, Cassette 161)
    - Marx in Soho by Howard Zinn (performed by Hal Fuller, directed by [Don Devecio]), undated (Box 74, Cassette 162)
    - Marx in Soho by Howard Zinn: Performance in Italian, undated (Box 74, Cassette 163)
    - New Hampshire Public Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview (edited), undated (Box 74, Cassette 164)
    - New Hampshire Public Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview (edited), undated (Box 74, Cassette 164 dup)
  - Subseries X:B: Audio Compact Disks, 1968-2009
    - Rev. Daniel Berrigan and Howard Zinn: Hanoi: Release of US Airmen (transfer from tape), 1968 (Box 75, Cd 165)
    - Howard Zinn at Maryville College, Fall 1969 (Box 75, Cd 166)
    - Howard Zinn's Last Class at Boston University, 1988 (Box 75, Cd 167)
    - Howard Zinn: "A People's History of the United States, A Lecture at Reed College" (AK Press Studio), 1998 (Box 75, Cd 168)
    - Howard Zinn: "A People's History of the United States, A Lecture at Reed College" (AK Press Studio), 1998 (Box 75, Cd 168 dup)
    - Noam Chomsky, Jimmy Tingle, Howard Zinn: "An Evening of Conversation, Confrontation and Comedy, A Benefit for Wellfleet Harbor Actors Theater", Aug 3, 2001 (Box 75, Cd 169)
    - Howard Zinn: "Heroes and Martyrs-Emma Goldman, Sacco and Vanzetti, and the Revolutionary Struggle" (AK Press Studio), 2001 (Box 75, Cd 170)
    - Howard Zinn: "Stories Hollywood Never Tells Us" (AK Press Studio), 2001 (Box 75, Cd 171)
    - Noam Chomsky and Howard Zinn (Photo CD), 2001-2002 (Box 75, Cd 172)
    - Howard Zinn: "Terrorism and War", Jun 17, 2002 (Box 75, Cd 173)
    - Howard Zinn: "Artists in a Time of War" (AK Press Audio), 2002 (Box 75, Cd 174)
    - Howard Zinn: "Civics Education: Patriotism of Skepticism" NPR's Justice Talking (The Annenberg Public Policy Center, University of Pennsylvania), 2002 (Box 75, Cd 175)
    - " A People's History of the United States, Highlights from the Twentieth Century" Read by Howard Zinn and Matt Damon (Harper Collins Publishers, Inc.) 4 CD set, 2002 (Box 75, Cd 177)
    - Howard Zinn (Photo CD), 2002-2008 (Box 75, Cd 178)
    - Howard Zinn: "USA and the War: Historic Perspective" (The Palestinian Radio Show at CKUT, 90.3 FM, Montreal, Quebec), Jan 20, 2003 (Box 75, Cd 179)
    - Howard Zinn Tribute - Voices from A People's History (92nd Street Y, New York City), Feb 23, 2003 (Box 75, Cd 180)
    - Howard Zinn: "History and War on Iraq" (Global Voices for Justice), Nov 3, 2003 (Box 75, Cd 181)
    - Howard Zinn: "Free and Fair" (KAOS, 89.2 FM, Olympia, WA), Dec 5, 2003 (Box 75, Cd 182)
    - Howard Zinn: "A Personal History" (Commonwealth Journal, Produced by WUMB Radio, University of Massachusetts, Boston), 2003 (Box 75, Cd 183)
    - Howard Zinn: "Why Civil Disobedience Matters" (KUCI, 88.9 FM, Irvine CA, Program "Justice or Just Us"), [2003] (Box 75, Cd 184)
    - Howard Zinn: "Artists in Times of War" (Cambridge Forum Radio), Jan 21, 2004 (Box 75, Cd 185)
    - Howard Zinn and Noam Chomsky: "Is There Hope in this Desperate Time?" (Radio Free Maine), Sep 27, 2004 (Box 75, Cd 186)
    - "The Outsider in American Politics" from the Marc Steiner Show "America's Future: 2004" (88.1 WYPR, Baltimore MD), Oct 7, 2004 (Box 75, Cd 187)
    - Howard Zinn et al: "Voices from a People's History" (New York, NY, Alternative Radio) Part 1, Oct 22, 2004 (Box 75, Cd 188)
    - Howard Zinn et al: "Voices from a People's History" (New York, NY, Alternative Radio) Part 2, Oct 22, 2004 (Box 75, Cd 189)
    - "Voices of a People's History": New York Society of Ethical Culture (2 CD set), Oct 22, 2004 (Box 75, Cd 190)
    - Howard Zinn: "Class and War in U.S. Society, A Critique" (Maxve Societal Press), Oct 27, 2004 (Box 75, Cd 191)
    - Howard Zinn: "Empire, Resistance and the War in Iraq" (Keynote Speech, Historians Against the War Conference, Austin, TX) Disk 1, Feb 17, 2006 (Box 75, Cd 192)
    - Howard Zinn and Anthony Arnove: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" (Lannan Readings and Conversations) Disk 2 of 2, Apr 26, 2006 (Box 75, Cd 193)
    - Howard Zinn: "The Inner Life of Democracy" (Cambridge Forum Radio), Oct 25, 2006 (Box 75, Cd 194)
    - Howard Zinn: "Overcoming Obstacles" (Boulder, CO, Alternative Radio), Nov 30, 2006 (Box 75, Cd 195)
    - Howard Zinn: "Overcoming Obstacles" (Boulder, CO Alternative Radio), Nov 30, 2006 (Box 75, Cd 195 dup)
    - "Readings from Voices of a People's History of the United States," (Seven Stories Press), 2006 (Box 75, Cd 196)
    - Performance of Marx in Soho with Robert Weick, Feb 15, 2007 (Box 75, Cd 197)
    - Howard Zinn: Question and Answer Session after Performance of Marx in Soho, Feb 15, 2007 (Box 75, Cd 198)
    - "Rebel Voices" Performances (stage adaptation of Voices of A People's History of the United States), Dec 11, 2007, Dec 16, 2007 (Box 75, Cd 199)
    - Howard Zinn: "Reflections on War" (Commonwealth Journal, Prodcued by WUMB Radio, University of Massachusetts, Boston), 2007 (Box 75, Cd 200)
    - Howard Zinn Readings (Photo CD), Jan 8, 2008 (Box 75, Cd 201)
    - "America, Empire of Liberty": Panel Discussion (Howard Zinn participating) on BBC Radio, Sep 2008 (Box 75, Cd 202)
    - "Sacco and Vanzetti 08" (companion piece to news report from Boston about Anarchists marking the 81st Anniversary of the execution of Sacco and Vanzetti), 2008 (Box 75, Cd 203)
    - "Living with the Consequences, The Legacy of the U.S. Policy in Nicaragua" (Photos of Page Proofs for Book) Part 1, [2008] (Box 75, Cd 204)
    - "Living with the Consequences, The Legacy of the U.S. Policy in Nicaragua" (Photos of Page Proofs for Book) Part 2, [2008] (Box 75, Cd 205)
    - "Americans Who Tell the Truth (and other recent Social Justice reports produced by Chuck U. Rosina)", Jan 2009-Apr 2009 (Box 75, Cd 206)
    - Marx a Roma Radio Performance (Also second disk that includes 2 bitmap images and an MP3 file), Jun 2009 (Box 75, Cd 207)
    - Marx in Soho Music Compilation, undated (Box 75, Cd 208)
    - Emma Act 2 Scenes 13-15, undated (Box 75, Cd 209)
    - Rossi Interview with Zinn (in Italian), undated (Box 75, Cd 210)
  - Subseries X:C: Audio Reel-to-Reel, 1957-1975
    - Howard Zinn: Spanish-American War, (Denver CO, 5 Inch), Jul 16, 1957 (Box 76, Reel 211)
    - Panel Discussion with Spelman College's First Exchange Students: Includes Sharon Passow, Mary Millen, Martha Thiessen, Mary Anne Peterson, Jackee Walken, May 1960 (Box 76, Reel 212)
    - Sit-In Showdown: Includes Music, Dance Performance and Comedy Tape 1, May 17, 1960 (Box 76, Reel 213)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): "China: Past and Present", "East and West", Lecture on Confucianism, Discussion of Menicus and Hsun-tze, Sep 26, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 214)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Session on the Chinese Language, Sep 27, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 215)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): "China: Past and Present," "Legalism and Confucianism" (also includes Hocking seminar on Confucianism), Sep 30, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 216)
    - Meet the Press: Ambassador Tsiang on Nationalist China / Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Chinese History, Oct 8, 1961/Oct 10, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 217)
    - Martin Luther King Jr. at Town Hall Meeting on Non-Violence (Atlanta University, GA) / Radio Broadcast: "The South: 1961" (Baptist Revival), Oct 12, 1961/Nov 12, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 218)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Owen Lattimore on China and Outer Mongolia, Oct 18, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 219)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Derk Bodde on Confucian Thought and Legal System, Nov 7, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 220)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Public Lecture - Derk Bodde on Old Society and New Forces, Nov 8, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 221)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Carl Holman and Elsie Edmondson on Chinese Literature, Nov 14, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 222)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Thomas Alitzer and Josephus Coan on Buddhism and Chinese Religion, Nov 28, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 223)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Alan Kagan on Chinese Music, Dec 12, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 224)
    - Domenico Scarlatti: Sonatas in E Major, G Minor and D Minor (5 Inch), Dec 24, 1961 (Box 76, Reel 225)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - "The Western Impact on China" (Kennedy, Duncan, and Rowley), Jan 2, 1962 (Box 76, Reel 226)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Benjamin Schwartz on China's Response to the West, Jan 9, 1962 (Box 76, Reel 227)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Jon Johnston on the Meeting of East and West, Jan 16, 1962 (Box 76, Reel 228)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Bingham Duncan and Howard Zinn on the Background of the 1911 Revolution, Feb 20, 1962 (Box 76, Reel 229)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Chet Huntley on NBC White Paper on China, Feb 25, 1962 (Box 76, Reel 230)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Howard Zinn on the May 4th Movement and the Rise of Communism, Feb 27, 1962 (Box 76, Reel 231)
    - Informal Discussion with Exchange Students at the Zinn House, Feb 1962 (Box 76, Reel 232)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): John K. Fairbank Lecture, Mar 6, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 233)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Howard Zinn on Marxist Theory, Mar 13, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 234)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Howard Zinn on Communist Theory, Mar 20, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 235)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Harry Steinmetz and Robert Cole on Thought Reform, Mar 27, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 236)
    - Robert Williams: Interviewed by March Schleiffer in Havana, Cuba (Broadcast Jun 5, 1962), Mar 1962 (Box 77, Reel 237)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Dr. Anthony Stampolis on the Economy of Communist China, Apr 5, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 238)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Herbert Ross and Carl Hollman on the Family in Communist China, Apr 10, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 239)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Ping-chia Kuo Lecture, Apr 17, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 240)
    - Richard Starr: Lecture on China and the Soviet Bloc, May 1, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 241)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar on China (includes William Worthy, Allan Cole, and Richard Walker), May 9, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 242)
    - Chris Allen in Dawson / Terrell, Sep 27, 1962 (Box 77, Reel 243)
    - Discussion with Young Unitarians: Staughton Lynd and Alice Walker, Oct 1962 (Box 77, Reel 244)
    - Lecture on Food Aid for China [Preview of Television Documentary], 1962 (Box 77, Reel 245)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Exchange Students in USSR (Includes Ed Morrell, Dick Judy and Mark Mancall) (Box 77, Reel 246)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Speak Chinese, Lessons 1-6 and Revised Lessons 1-6 (Institute of Far Eastern Languages, Yale University) (Box 77, Reel 247)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Speak Chinese, Lessons 7-15 (Institute of Far Eastern Languages, Yale University) (Box 77, Reel 248)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Speak Chinese, Lessons 16-22 (Institute of Far Eastern Languages, Yale University) (Box 77, Reel 249)
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Speak Chinese, Lessons 23-24 and Vocabulary Review Lessons 1-24 (Institute of Far Eastern Languages, Yale University) (Box 77, Reel 250)
    - Young Americans for Freedom: Debate - Shall the House Committee on Un-American Activities be Abolished? (includes Fulton Lewis III, Howard Zinn and Nancy Perkins, Emory University, Atlanta GA), Feb 11, 1963 (Box 77, Reel 251)
    - Social Science Club Meeting: Liberty and Spelman College (Darcas Bait, Chairman) Tape 1, Mar 11, 1963 (Box 77, Reel 252)
    - Social Science Club Meeting: Liberty and Spelman College (Darcas Bait, Chairman) Tape 2, Mar 11, 1963 (Box 77, Reel 253)
    - Social Science Club Meeting: Liberty and Spelman College (Darcas Bait, Chairman) Tape 3, Mar 11, 1963 (Box 77, Reel 254)
    - Town Meeting: What Should We Do About Cuba?: Includes Staughton Lynd, Robert Brisbane and Robert Trucker (Atlanta University, GA), Mar 21, 1963 (Box 78, Reel 255)
    - Meeting: Includes Mrs. Pilcher, John Novack and Paul Jourdan (Greenwood, MS), Aug 15, 1963 (Box 78, Reel 256)
    - Meeting: Includes Kids from County Jail and Marchman (Greenwood, MS), Aug 16, 1963 (Box 78, Reel 257)
    - Stokely Carmichael: Lecture (Greenwood, MS), Aug 1963 (Box 78, Reel 258)
    - Interview Conducted by Howard Zinn with SNCC Workers (Selma, AL) / [Bruce Bovington] Interviewed by Alan Ribback, Oct 6, 1963/Sep 29, 1963 (Box 78, Reel 259)
    - Malcolm X: Message to the Grass Roots (King Solomon Baptist Church, Detroit, MI 5 Inch), [Nov 10, 1963] (Box 78, Reel 260)
    - Interview with Charlie Cogg, SNCC / Singing at Staff Meeting (Greenville, MS), Nov 14, 1963 (Box 78, Reel 261)
    - SNCC Washington Conference: Food and Jobs (Saturday Evening Dinner), Dec 1, 1963 (Box 78, Reel 262)
    - SNCC Washington Conference: Government Agencies, Dec 1, 1963 (Box 78, Reel 263)
    - SNCC Washington Conference: Bayard Rustin Speech, Dec 1, 1963 (Box 78, Reel 264)
    - SNCC Washington Conference: Bob Moses on Life article on SNCC / TV Program NET on White Northerners and Segregation, Dec 1, 1963/Dec 2, 1963 (Box 78, Reel 265)
    - Southern Report on Police Brutality (Gasden, AL 5 Inch), 1963 (Box 78, Reel 266)
    - Edgar Snow: Lecture on China (Guest Lecturer in Howard Zinn's Class), 1963 (Box 78, Reel 267)
    - Howard Zinn: Speech Haverford College (Haverford, PA), Feb 1964 (Box 78, Reel 268)
    - NBC-TV Program on James Chaney, Andrew Goodman and Michael Schwerner (Murdered Mississippi Civil Rights Workers), Jun 27, 1964 (Box 78, Reel 269)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - Remarks at Syracuse University on the Communist Challenge in Southeast Asia, Aug 5, 1964 (Box 78, Reel 270)
    - Howard Zinn: Interview on SNCC, The New Abolitionists and The Southern Mystique, [1964] (Box 78, Reel 271)
    - Vietnam Debate: McGeorge Bundy vs Hans Morgenthau, Jun 1965 (Box 78, Reel 272)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - State of the Union Address Part 1, Jan 12, 1966 (Box 78, Reel 273)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - State of the Union Address Part 2, Jan 12, 1966 (Box 78, Reel 274)
    - Dean Rusk: Speech (Indiana University, IN), Oct 31, 1967 (Box 78, Reel 275)
    - WFIU: Howard Zinn - Convocation Address on the Necessity of Immediate Withdrawal from Vietnam (Indiana University, Bloomington, IN) Tape 1, Dec 1, 1967 (Box 78, Reel 276)
    - WFIU: Howard Zinn - Convocation Address on the Necessity of Immediate Withdrawl from Vietnam (Indiana University, Bloomington, IN) Tape 2, Dec 1, 1967 (Box 78, Reel 277)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - Address to the American People (Master), Mar 31, 1968 (Box 79, Reel 278)
    - National Archives and Records Service: Lyndon B. Johnson - Address to the American People (Copy), Mar 31, 1968 (Box 79, Reel 279)
    - WDET: Howard Zinn - "Abolitionist Motivations: Pro and Con" (Wayne State University Centennial, Detroit, MI), 1968 (Box 79, Reel 280)
    - WHPK: Marlene Dixon Press Conference on University of Chicago's Decision Not to Rehire her (Includes Sit-In, 10 1/2 Inches), Feb 12, 1969 (Box 79, Reel 281)
    - Abbie Hoffman (Harvard University Cambridge, MA), Fall 1969 (Box 79, Reel 282)
    - Howard Zinn: Speech (Moratorium to End the War in Vietnam Day), Oct 15, 1969 (Box 79, Reel 283)
    - National Archives and Record Service: Richard Nixon - Address to the Nation on the War in Vietnam, Nov 3, 1969 (Box 79, Reel 284)